Guide to the Voices of Contemporary Art Records MSS.601
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II. VoCA Talks Series, 2013-2019; 1644 Gigabytes on 4424 computer files
  - Tara Sabharwal -- Other Materials, 2017-2019; cuid28814 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_135)
  - Tara Sabharwal -- Presentation, 2017-2019; cuid28815 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_136)
  - Tara Sabharwal -- Promotion, 2017-2019; cuid28816 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_137)
  - Tara Sabharwal -- Transcript, 2017-2019; cuid28817 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_138)
  - Tara Sabharwal -- Videos, 2017-2019; cuid28818 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_139)
  - Ted Kurahara -- Event Documentation, 2018-2019; cuid28700 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_140)
  - Ted Kurahara -- Images, 2018-2019; cuid28819 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_141)
  - Ted Kurahara -- Other Materials, 2018-2019; cuid28820 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_142)
  - Ted Kurahara -- Presentation, 2018-2019; cuid28821 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_143)
  - Ted Kurahara -- Promotion, 2018-2019; cuid28822 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_144)
  - Ted Kurahara -- Transcript, 2018-2019; cuid28823 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_145)
  - Ted Kurahara -- Videos, 2018-2019; cuid28824 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_146)
  - Tory Fair -- Event Documentation, 2019; cuid28701 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_147)
  - Tory Fair -- Images, 2019; cuid28825 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_148)
  - Tory Fair -- Presentation, 2019; cuid28826 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_149)
  - Tory Fair -- Promotion, 2019; cuid28827 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_150)
  - Tory Fair -- Transcript, 2019; cuid28828 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_151)
  - Tory Fair -- Videos, 2019; cuid28829 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_152)
  - Vito Acconci -- Event Documentation, 2017-2019; cuid28702 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_153)
  - Vito Acconci -- Images, 2017-2019; cuid28830 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_154)
  - Vito Acconci -- Other Materials, 2017-2019; cuid28831 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_155)
  - Vito Acconci -- Presentation, 2017-2019; cuid28832 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_156)
  - Vito Acconci -- Promotion, 2017-2019; cuid28833 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_157)
  - Vito Acconci -- Transcript, 2017-2019; cuid28834 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_158)
  - Vito Acconci -- Videos, 2017-2019; cuid28835 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_159)
- Series III. VoCA Journal, 2015-2019; 5.13 Gigabytes on 424 computer files
  This series is arranged chronologically by journal issue.
  This series consists of electronic records, the majority of which are pdfs, documenting the publication of VoCA Journal between 2015-2020. Materials include drafts of articles, images used in the publication, editors notes, and copies of the issue's digital layout.
  - Issue 1, 2015; cuid29426 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_169)
  - Issue 2, 2015-2016; cuid29427 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_170)
  - Issue 3, 2016; cuid29428 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_171)
  - Issue 4, 2016; cuid29429 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_172)
  - Issue 5, 2017; cuid29430 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_173)
  - Issue 6, 2017; cuid29431 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_174)
  - Issue 7, 2017; cuid29432 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_175)
  - Issue 8, 2018; cuid29433 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_176)
  - Issue 9, 2019; cuid29434 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_177)
  - Issue 10, 2020; cuid29435 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_178)
  - Table of Contents, 2020; cuid29436 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_179)